lasership.com 2019-07-08

# LaserShip® Privacy Policy

#### LaserShip takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

### SCOPE

This privacy policy covers how LaserShip treats personal information that we collect and receive via this website, portals accessed through or associated with this website, or other associated links maintained by LaserShip. Personal information is identifiable information about an individual, e.g. a name, address, email address, phone number, or payment information and includes information related to past use of LaserShip services. We may obtain personal information in connection with various activities such as (i) your use of our website, portals, associated links and applications, (ii) shipping activities, including delivery and pickup of shipments, and (iii) requests to track shipments or answer questions.

This privacy policy does not apply to information that is or becomes publicly available, e.g. listed in online directories, which relates to the practices of companies that LaserShip does not own or control, or regarding actions of individuals that LaserShip does not employ or manage.

### INFORMATION COLLECTION

#### General

#### General Collection

LaserShip collects personal information when (i) a LaserShip account is set up, (ii) you register as a user of LaserShip’s services, (iii) LaserShip services are used, (iv) you register to receive job information on LaserShip’s Careers page or by using other links maintained by LaserShip, (v) you provide information to inquire about driving for LaserShip on our Drivers page or using other links maintained by LaserShip, (vi) you access a LaserShip portal, (vii) when you enter orders, (viii) when you track orders, and ( ix) you enter LaserShip promotions or respond to surveys. 

The types of personal information we may obtain include:

  * Individual and business contact information (such as name, physical address, email address, and telephone or fax number)
  * Shipping information (such as (i) customers name, physical address, email address and telephone number), (ii) LaserShip account number, and (iii) information given to us that helps us access locations to which we provide service
  * Names, email addresses and telephone numbers of others to whom we are asked to send information
  * Username, password and other credentials used to access our products and services
  * Other personal information that may be provided to us by you
  * When we pick up or deliver a shipment, we may obtain location data about you and your customers

### Device and Mobile App[s] Information

We collect information about your computer, phone, tablet or other devices when you access our website or use our services, including connection type, operating system, browser type, IP address, device identifiers. You can disable the collection of much of this information through the settings of your device or through your operating system.

If you visit our website and associated links and portals using a mobile device, we may also collect the geographic location of your mobile device if you use certain features of our apps.

### USE OF INFORMATION

LaserShip uses personal information for the following general purposes: (i) pick up, deliver and track shipments, (ii) process and collect payments, (iii) provide customer support and respond to and communicate with you about your requests, inquiries, questions and comments, (iv) establish and manage your account, (v) review job and engagement inquiries, (vii) for users with portal access, interact with you in a capacity as dictated by your user status, and (viii) communicate about, and administer your participation in, special events, programs, surveys, contests, sweepstakes, and other offers or promotions, including sending you our newsletter.

In addition, we also may:

  * Send information to your contacts if you ask us to do so
  * Process claims we receive in connection with our services
  * Operate, evaluate and improve our business
  * Perform data analyses
  * Protect against, identify and prevent fraud and other criminal activity, claims and other liabilities
  * Comply with applicable legal requirements and our policies

### ABOUT LASERSHIP PHOTO ON DELIVERY

LaserShip may take a photo on delivery when a package is left unattended. The photo will focus on the placement of the package and immediately disappears from the driver’s device. Capturing delivery photos is intended to help customers see that their package was safely delivered and where. If a photo on delivery is captured, it may show up when you track a package from lasership.com.

Accessing a delivery photo, to the extent this feature is or becomes available, requires signing in with your user name and password on the lasership.com website. We may use delivery photos to verify delivery location, audit for quality purposes, or troubleshoot what happened to a package.

### INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE

LaserShip does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other individuals or nonaffiliated companies, except to the extent necessary to provide the services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of LaserShip's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

We may transfer information about you if LaserShip is acquired by or merged with another company, including in the event of a reorganization, liquidation or dissolution. In this event, LaserShip will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

### HOW WE STORE AND SECURE YOUR INFORMATION

We use data hosting service providers in the United States to host the information we collect, and we use technical measures to secure your data.

We will undertake reasonable steps to protect all information, from unauthorized or accidental access, disclosure, misuse or processing, or from alteration, destruction, or loss. However, because no security measures are perfect or impenetrable, we cannot guarantee the security of information you submit to us.

### RETENTION OF YOUR INFORMATION

We may retain your questions and feedback in order to improve our services. Do not send us any information, ideas, suggestions, proposals or comments that you consider confidential or that you wish to be treated as confidential. If you no longer want us to use or retain personal information you provided to us, you may contact us **click here** and request that we delete that such personal information from our records.

Your personal information will not be stored for longer than is necessary for which it was collected or as required under applicable retention policies or practices, or as otherwise may be permitted or required in accordance with applicable law.

### COOKIES

LaserShip may set and access LaserShip cookies on your computer. A "cookie" is a text file that websites send to a visitor's computer or other Internet-connected device to uniquely identify the visitor's browser or to store information or settings in the browser.

LaserShip may link certain data elements we have collected through cookies, such as your browser information, with other information we have obtained about you. LaserShip also may use third-party analytics tools that collect information about visitor traffic on our websites or apps.

Your browser may tell you how to be notified when you receive certain types of cookies or how to restrict or disable certain types of cookies. Please note, however, that without cookies you may not be able to use all of the features of our websites or apps.

### MARKETING COMMUNICATIONS

If you register as a user of a LaserShip Web Account, you will be asked if you would like to receive marketing and other informational communications from us. You can choose to opt-out from receiving marketing communications from us at this stage or, at any time, by sending us a message with your request. **Click here** to contact us.

### CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide services to you or in order to do their jobs. However, information that is located on the outside of a package or letter may be visible to others.

We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information about you. Depending on your user status, your LaserShip Account Information may be password-protected. In certain areas LaserShip may use industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions.

### INTERNATIONAL USERS

The website is hosted, and the services are performed in the U.S. and are intended for U.S. customers. If you are physically located in one of the 28 European Union Countries, please do not submit any personal information to us. If you believe you may have disclosed personally identifiable information to us, please contact us at (see the How to Contact Us link below) and we will remove it. If you are a consumer accessing the website or our services from Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use and disclosure that differ from U.S. laws, your continued use of our website or services, which are governed by U.S. law and these terms, indicates your consent to transfer of your information to the U.S.

### CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

Because protecting the privacy of young children is especially important, we do not knowingly collect or maintain information from or about persons under 13 years of age. No part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. If you are under 13, do not use or access the website at any time or in any manner. If we learn that personal information of persons under 13 has been collected without verified parental consent, we will take appropriate steps to delete this information.

### YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS (FOR CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS ONLY)

Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code requires select businesses to disclose policies relating to the sharing of certain categories of customers' personal information with third parties. These businesses are required to accept requests for disclosures of these policies from customers but are only required to honor one request per calendar year. Businesses have thirty (30) days to respond to each inquiry to the designated address. Each inquiring customer will receive an explanation of the categories of customer information shared and the names and addresses of any third party businesses. In limited circumstances, customers' failure to submit requests in the manner specified will not require a response from the business.

If you are a California resident, you may request such information from us by sending a letter to the address listed below. In your letter, please provide your name, address and email address, as well as a request that we provide such information to you, by using the following or similar language, “I request that LaserShip provide its third-party information sharing disclosures required by section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code.”

**LaserShip, Inc.  
1912 Woodford Road  
Vienna, VA 22182  
Attention: Legal Department**

### ACCESS AND CORRECTION

Depending on your user status, you may access certain personal information we maintain about you or update or correct inaccuracies in that information through your account or by contacting us as indicated in the "How To Contact Us" section of this Privacy Notice. To help protect your privacy and maintain security, we will take steps to verify your identity before granting you access to the information. In addition, if you believe that personal information we maintain about you is inaccurate, subject to applicable law, you may have the right to request that we correct or amend the information by contacting us as indicated below.

### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

LaserShip may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your LaserShip account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

### HOW TO CONTACT US

If you have any questions or concerns about this Policy, please **click here** to send us a message.
